The loading operations are finish, half ready for take-off.
装载作业已经完成  起飞准备已过半
There a problem, Sergeant?
有问题吗 中士？
No, sir...
不 长官...
Sorry, I was just, uh...
对不起 我只是...
Get your shit together. We lift off in five.
把东西收拾好 5分钟后起飞
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
Hey, you're HALO qualified, yeah?
嘿 你有 "高跳低开" 资格的 是吗？
HALO?
高跳低开？
No, sir.
没有 长官
Are we doing a HALO jump?
我们要 "高跳低开" 吗？
You'll be fine.
你会没事的
I'd go Fruit Loops.
我会选择水果圈
My daughter loves them.
我女儿很喜欢那个
Lieutenant Mitchell reporting. I repeat.
米切尔中尉报告 重复一遍
Lieutenant Mitchell reporting.
米切尔中尉报告
Ah, fuck.
妈的
苏禄海 菲律宾
Going after a CIA asset that's been captured.
营救一名被俘虏的中情局特工
The plan is to extract him with minimal casualties.
计划是以最小的伤亡救出他
He was gathering intel on Alexander Petrov, a Russian arms dealer
他正在收集俄罗斯军火商和前克格勃
and former KGB.
亚历山大·彼得罗夫的情报
What's up?
怎么了？
That your family?
那是你家人吗？
Nah, just a pic that came with the helmet.
不 只是头盔里附送的一张照片
Yeah. Wife and kids.
是的 老婆和孩子
Nice.
不错
Are those the new 5.11 tactical gloves?
那是新的 5.11 战术手套吗？
You know the ones with the Kevlar knit?
凯夫拉纤维编织的那种？
Yeah, yeah. Kevlar knit.
是啊 是啊 凯夫拉纤维
Awesome.
棒极了
JTAC,
空管员
just try to relax, okay?
尽量放松 好吗？
内利斯空军基地 拉斯维加斯
Right back the other way on the Euro and gets that one to go.
直接回到欧洲队的半场 将球投进
And the whistle too...
哨声也随即响起
That bad?
这么糟糕？
Yeah, that bad.
是啊 就这么糟
Do you wanna talk about it?
你想谈谈吗？
Wanna hug?
想拥抱一下吗？
We can hug.
我们可以拥抱一下
You need me?
你找我吗？
Yeah, I wanted to ask you something, but...
是的 我想问你点事 但是...
Okay. Coffee?
好的 要咖啡吗？
Sure.
当然
Okay.
好的
Yeah.
是啊
Cool.
酷毙了
So, uh,
那么
you know the wedding's coming up, right?
你知道婚礼快到了吧？
Yes, I do. Twenty-third.
是的 我知道 二十三号
That's right.
没错
You're not gonna change the date, are you?
你不会改变日期吧？
What?
什么？
I've got everything organized. I got the kids in place.
我把一切都安排得井井有条 我把孩子们都安排好了
I got the ex-wives in place.
我把前妻们都安排好了
- Lucy will be out of the hospital. - Reaper.
- 露西要出院了 - 死神
I'm not going to change the date.
我不会改变日期的
I, um, actually wanted to talk to you about something else.
其实我想跟你说点别的事
I wanted to ask...
我想问问...
Who moved my shit?
谁动了我的东西？
Airman...
飞手...
who moved my shit?
谁动了我的东西？
Huh?
啊？
Coffee pods.
咖啡豆
I... I don't know, sir. I use the drip.
我不知道 长官 我喝的是蒸馏的
Well, I can't trust a word you say then, can I?
那我就不能相信你说的话了 是吧？
Yeah.
是啊
I take the time.
我花时间
Every goddamn morning.
每个该死的早晨
I do it
我摆好
for efficiency,
提高效率
easy recognition,
易于识别
and organization.
和摆放
Is it appreciated?
有人感激吗
No.
不
Is it respected？
有人尊重吗
I think not.
我想没有
But I do it
但我还是摆好了
for the morale
为了中队的
of the squadron.
士气
You were saying?
你刚才说什么？
Op starts in 15.
Yeah, yeah. I thought you wanted to talk about something.
是啊 是啊 我以为你想谈点什么
It can wait.
不着急
Shit.
妈的
You lose something?
你丢东西了？
Ah, just my cereal.
啊 只是我的麦片
Your what?
你的什么？
Froot Loops.
水果圈
I had a box of Froot Loops. I don't know what I did with it.
我有一包水果圈 不知道放哪里去了
Jesus Christ, Air Force.
上帝啊 空管员
Barely started this op and you're already sweating about a box of Frosted Flakes.
还没开始行动 你就已经为一盒糖霜薄饼捏一把汗了
No, no. It was... it was Froot Loops.
不 不 是...是....是水果圈
Huh?
啊？
Froot Loops, not Frosted Flakes.
是水果圈 不是糖霜薄饼
This kid for real?
这小子是说真的吗？
Don't be an asshole.
别那么混蛋
That's cute.
真可爱
Thanks, man.
谢谢
Fucking Fruit Loops.
该死的水果圈
How old are you, Air Force?
你多大了 空管员？
Twenty-seven.
Ah...
啊...
Bishop, how old's your daughter now? Twenty?
主教 你女儿多大了？20岁？
You should set Air Force up on a date.
你应该给空军安排个约会
Yeah. I will shoot you in the dick, Abell. I swear to God.
我会打烂你的小弟弟 埃贝 我发誓
No, honey.
不 亲爱的
I can't.
我做不到
I can't come.
我不能来
'Cause I gotta be here
因为我必须在这里
at work. Yeah.
要工作 是啊
Look, just get your sister to go.
听着 叫你姐姐去吧
What about your mom?
你妈妈呢？
All right. Well, why don't you call...?
好吧 那你为什么不打电话....？
Oh, you called Judy? Uh...
哦 你给朱迪打过电话了？呃...
look, okay, okay.
你看 好吧 好吧
If it's only a couple of things, that's fine.
如果只是几件事情 那也没关系
That's fine. But right now, I gotta go
没关系 但现在 我得走了
'cause I got a mission, yeah?
因为我有任务 好吗？
Zegler a little teardrop.
泽格勒的眼泪都要流出来了
You know I don't like that shot in college, right?
你知道我不喜欢大学时的那一个投篮 对吧？
it's made about 37 percent of the time.
约有 37% 的时间是这样做的
Fuck.
妈的
Zegler just settled for a tough floater on the first side of the floor.
泽格勒只是在地板的这一边投中了一个高难度的花哨球
Guys.
伙计们
I got a favor to ask you.
我想请你们帮个忙
My wife is pregnant.
我妻子怀孕了
While I'm on OP, if she goes into labor, she's gonna call that phone.
当我在执行任务的时候 如果她要生了 她就会打那个电话
All right?
行吗？
You need to answer it,
你们必须接听一下
and you need to come and get me.
然后过来告诉我
Copy?
听到了吗？
Thank you very much.
非常感谢
And why don't we just keep this volume down to a low level?
我们为什么不把音量降得低点呢？
Because this is a professional work environment.
因为这是一个专业的工作环境
Now, now. Just because your team
现在 现在 就因为你的队伍
delivered the biggest choke in March Madness history,
创造了 "疯狂三月" 历史上最大的辉煌
doesn't mean the rest of us can't still enjoy ourselves.
但这并不意味着我们其他人不能尽情享受
It's about Lucy. Virgil, it's important.
是露西的事 维吉尔 这很重要
I know.
我知道
Notice the, uh,
注意这个
pseudofolliculitis
假性毛囊炎
barbae hasn't
还没有
cleared up.
被清除掉
Not yet, sir. No.
还没有 长官 还没有
Well, you just let me know when you're ready to shave.
好吧 你准备刮胡子的时候告诉我一声就行了
I will, sir.
我会的 长官
All right.
好的
- Go, Vols! - Go, Vols!
- 加油 狼队 - 加油 狼队
Warhawk, this is Blackbird approaching drop zone.
战鹰 这是黑鸟 正在接近空投区
Headed to 15,000 feet.
降到15000英尺
Six minutes to the DZ.
六分钟后到达空投区
Winds are five knots and to the southeast.
风速五节 东南风
Skies are clear.
天空晴朗
Happy hunting.
狩猎愉快
All right, boys. Six minutes.
好了 孩子们 还有六分钟
Here we go.
开始了
Fruit Loop, now's the time to be checking your weapon.
水果圈 现在是时候检查你的武器了
I'm good.
我很好
Not your Gameboy. Your actual weapon.
不是你的游戏机 你真正的武器
Hey, look, I'm in charge of the drone. So...
嘿 听着 无人机归我管 所以...
if we wind up in a situation and I'm shooting,
如果我们陷入困境 而我要开枪
we got big fucking problems.
我们就有大麻烦了
You're not wrong.
你没说错
You're not wrong. JTAC's only good for one thing and that is... "Bringing the rain."
你没说错 空管员只擅长一件事 那就是..."空中支援"
Is this your first mission in theater, JTAC?
这是你第一次在战区执行任务吗 空管员？
Second.
第二次
But first with operators.
但是第一次和行动队员一起
What?
什么？
Hell, I'll say it. Um...
见鬼 我来说吧 嗯...
we're about to head into a shit storm.
我们即将陷入一场腥风血雨
You still look like you kind of need someone to wipe your ass.
你看起来还是好像需要别人帮你擦屁股
So just... do me a favor.
所以....帮我个忙
Keep up and don't fuck up.
跟上 别搞砸了
Last thing we need in this op is to have to save your ass.
在这次行动中 我们最不需要的就是救你的命
Nah, he's good.
不 他没事的
Hey,
嘿
remember your training.
记住你的训练
Talk to the planes.
与飞机联络
When they start dropping bombs, make sure it's on the bad guys.
当他们开始扔炸弹时 确保炸的是坏人
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
You're not going to need these.
你不需要这些了
This is a sterilized op.
这是一个消毒操作
Be advised we are approaching...
请注意 我们即将...
All right, boys. Let's put our masks on. Let's get to work.
好了 孩子们戴上面罩 开始工作了
Hey, JTAC,
嘿 空管员
this might sound stupid but don't forget to breathe, yeah?
这听起来可能很蠢 但别忘了呼吸 好吗？
Stay on your comms.
保持通讯
When that hits 3,000,
等到了 3000 米时
deploy your chute.
就展开降落伞
It's just the same as airborne,
这和空中飞行是一样的
only way fucking higher.
只有他妈的更高
Good to go.
可以走了
I'll see you fuckers on the beach.
我们海滩上见
Yee-haw.
咦哈
Hey,
嘿
walk in the park.
去公园散步了
Fuck.
妈的
惊  天  激  战
字幕:Dex7er  公众号:值得看的
You good?
你还好吗？
Let's go. Come on. Get up.
我们走 快点 起来
That ridge.
那个山脊
Four clicks by 0800.
有四公里 八点前要到
Let's go. Let's move.
我们走 我们走
All right.
好的
Sir,
先生
Thank you, Miller.
谢谢你 米勒
Okay, team has landed.
好了 队伍已经着陆
Operators are en route.
行动人员已在途中
The drone is ten mics out from rendezvous point
无人机距离会合点有十公里的距离
and Warhawk is switching comms.
战鹰正在切换通讯
This carriage is about to turn into a pumpkin.
这辆马车就要变成南瓜了
This is not my chair.
这不是我的椅子
Yes, it is.
是的 就是
No, it is not.
不 不是
Oh, my god, Reaper, I did not take your chair.
天哪 死神 我没抢你的椅子
I know you didn't take my chair.
我知道你没有抢我的椅子
It will be these commie assholes from Shadow Flight.
估计是 "影子航班 "的这些共产主义混蛋
You finished?
你说完了吗？
No, I'm not.
不 我没有
Eat a bag of dicks.
吃屎去吧
Now I'm finished.
现在我说完了
Okay.
好吧
All right, let's take this lady to the dance.
好了 我们带这位女士去跳舞吧
Playboy 06, this is Reaper 1-0 checking in...
花花公子0-6 这是死神1-0 报到...
You have 1 MQ-9 in the air.
空中有 1 架 MQ-9
1 by BLU 118 on board. Eight hours of playtime ahead.
携有一枚118 燃烧弹. 八小时的游戏时间
Reaper 1-0, this is Playboy 0-6. Stand by for grid, over.
死神1-0 这里是花花公子0-6 等待接收坐标 完毕
Roger. Standing by.
收到 随时待命
Grid as follows,
坐标如下
…November, Victor, 7, Niner, 5-7-1-8.
....N V 7 9 5-7-1-8
That's a friendly grid.
这是一个友方坐标
Roger, Playboy. I have visual on friendly grid.
收到 花花公子 我拿到了友方坐标的视野
I am your eyes in the sky and the bringer of doom.
我是你们的天眼和厄运使者
Over.
完毕
Reaper is airborne. Our location is confirmed.
死神已升空 我们的位置已确认
What's the ordinance?
有什么配备？
Two hellfire's and a BLUE-118, sir.
两枚地狱火和一枚118燃烧弹 长官
Lose the sir shit. I work for a living.
不用客套 我以工作为生
It's Sugar or Sug.
叫我甜心或者糖
All right.
好的
Makes him feel old.
让他觉得自己老了
He is old.
他是老了
Thanks, Air Force.
谢谢 空管员
距离目标区域8公里
Hey, JTAC.
嘿 空管员
What rock did they find you under?
他们是在哪个石头缝里找到你的？
In Guam on a training exercise.
在关岛参加训练演习
Missed the flight out.
错过了离开的航班
That was
那是
nine hours ago.
九小时前
How'd you miss the flight?
你怎么没赶上飞机？
I had some stomach issues.
我的胃有点问题
Wait.
等等
You're here 'cause you had the shits?
你来这里是因为拉肚子？
Well, I hope you got that all cleared out.
好了 我希望你都拉干净了
You shit your pants on an op,
你要是在行动中拉裤子了
that stain will follow you for life.
这个污点将伴随你一生
Did you get briefed?
你收到简报了吗？
Yeah, but I'm a little confused.
是的 但我有点困惑
What about?
哪里困惑？
Well, I'm not tier one.
好吧 我不是一线人员
Yet he walks amongst us.
然而 他却走在我们中间
I thought operators don't go out without tier one personnel.
我以为没有一线人员 行动人员是不会出动的
We don't.
是不会
So why am I here?
那我为什么会在这里？
A JSOC asset disappeared two weeks ago.
两周前 一名联合特别行动小组成员失踪
Believed to be kidnapped.
据信被绑架了
We've got intel on a possible locale.
我们得到了一个可能地点的情报
So this is a rescue op?
所以这是一次救援行动？
Potentially.
有可能
Ah.
啊
You can never keep up with these CIA spooks.
你永远跟不上这些中情局间谍的脚步
Either way... here we are.
无论如何....我们来了这里
So to answer your question...
那么回答你的问题
no, you shouldn't be here.
不 你不应该在这里
And, yes,
是的
Delta doesn't usually go out without their tier one personnel.
三角洲部队通常不会在没有一级人员的情况下外出
And, yes,
是的
if our guy is here,
如果我们的人在这
then we'll go in and fucking get him.
那我们就进去把他救出来
Translation...
翻译...
step up your game.
升级你的游戏
I need someone to cover.
我需要有人掩护
Yeah.
是啊
I gotta check in with Lucy.
我得去看看露西
How's she doing?
她怎么样了？
She's fantastic.
她太棒了
Got the baby brain going on though.
不过 一孕傻三年
I gotta repeat everything five times.
我得把每件事都重复五遍
It's amazing.
太神奇了
Absolutely huge.
绝对神奇
Got the same thing about this wedding.
我对这场婚礼也有同感
Uh, it's understandable.
可以理解
There's a lot of detail.
有很多细节
You think about it.
你想想看
A wedding is probably the greatest social ritual humanity has.
婚礼可能是人类最盛大的社交仪式
You know,
你知道的
most important day of your life.
你一生中最重要的一天
Might as well get it right.
最好做对了
You're only going to do it once.
你只能做一次
Reaper, you've been married four times.
死神 你已经结过四次婚了
Yeah, that's just me though.
是啊 这只是我这样
I'm a romantic.
我是个浪漫主义者
What did you want to ask me before?
你之前想问我什么？
Oh, I...
哦 我...
Hold that thought.
稍安勿躁
Thank you, Miller.
谢谢你 米勒
Reaper.
死神
距离目标区域3公里
Hey, what's up?
嘿 怎么了？
Ah, this fucking frag is a pain in my ass.
啊 这该死的碎片真让我头疼
Thought you got that patched up.
我还以为你修好了呢
I did.
是修好了
So why are you still bitching about it?
那你为什么还在抱怨呢？
There's still a fucking hole in my leg, asshole.
我的腿上还有个洞呢 混蛋
What happened?
怎么了？
I.E.D.
地雷
Some kid triggered it from half a click out.
有个孩子在半米外触发了它
We never stood a chance.
我们根本没有机会
Therein lies the problem, Fruit Loop.
这就是问题所在 水果圈
All this tech,
所有这些技术
it takes the human element out of warfare.
都需要将人的因素排除在战争之外
And what happens when all that shit fails?
如果这一切都失败了 会发生什么？
Well...
嗯...
Well, what?
怎么了？
I don't know. I mean,
我不知道 我是说
I think this tech saves lives.
我认为这项技术能拯救生命
In a way, it's takes the barbaric nature out of it.
从某种程度上说 它带走了野蛮的本性
Barbaric nature?
野蛮的本性？
Lipstick on a pig.
换汤不换药
You really think you dropping a bomb on 50 people is any better
你真的认为你们向 50 人投掷炸弹
than us shooting them in the head?
比我们朝他们头上开枪好？
No.
不
No. War is barbaric.
不 战争是野蛮的
It ain't never gonna fucking change.
这他妈的永远不会改变
It already has.
已经变了
Listen up, Fruit Loop.
听好了 水果圈
Let me tell you a story.
我给你讲个故事吧
You can fight with all your robots and your reapers and cell phones you want.
你可以用你的机器人 无人机和手机进行战斗
The end of the day,
最后有一天
when the technology fails
当技术失效
and all your...
和你所有的...
your batteries and your bullets and your bombs run out, you know,
你的电池 子弹和炸弹用完了 你知道吗？
and the fucking sun explodes,
然后他妈的太阳就爆炸了
war comes down to one very simple thing.
战争归根结底是一件非常简单的事情
And that's man killing man.
这就是人杀人
Just takes one shit day to change your whole perspective.
只需要一个糟糕的一天 就能改变你的整个观点
That's a fact.
这是事实
Yeah.
是啊
Welcome to the land of bad.
欢迎来到糟糕地带
Fucking great story, man.
真他妈是个好故事
Really fucking good, rich and compelling.
真他妈不错 内容丰富 引人入胜
What do you got?
有什么发现？
I got movement.
我这有动静
Hundred meters.
百米以外
Just the other side of those rocks.
就在岩石的另一边
I need eyes over that ridge. Hundred meters northeast.
我需要看到山脊那边 东北方向100米
Reaper 1-0, this is Playboy 0-6.
死神 1-0 这是花花公子 0-6
Got suspicious movement a hundred meters northeast of our position.
我们位置东北方向一百米处有可疑动静
Can you check it out?
你能去看看吗？
Roger that, Playboy. Standby.
收到 花花公子 待命
Hundred meters southeast.
东南方百米处
Got good handshake.
信号很清楚
Reaper 1-0, can you zoom in?
收割者 1-0 能放大吗？
Copy that.
收到
Yeah, oh, that's sexy.
是啊 真性感
Pan left, 50 meters.
向左平移 50 米
What the fuck?
搞什么鬼？
Reaper, I'm hollow, over.
死神 我失联了 完毕
Roger. Standby.
收到 待命
Systems malfunction.
系统故障
Goddamn piece of shit.
该死的废物
Playboy, we have a systems malfunction on the bird.
花花公子 我们的无人机出了点故障
Copy that. Is the pod inop?
收到 失灵了吗？
That is an a-firm, Playboy. We got to get this piece of shit back to base.
确定 花花公子 我们得把这破玩意带回基地
Is another bird available?
还有别的鸟吗？
That is a negative.
没有
We'll fix this one up and get it back to you stat.
我们会把这个修好 并及时送回这里
Reapers down. No other UAV's available.
死神完了 没有其他无人机可用
Broken Reaper, huh?
坏了的死神 是吧？
Ain't that some fuckin' irony?
这不是他妈的讽刺吗？
Looks like we're gonna have to clear this ridge the old-fashioned way.
看来我们得用老办法清理山脊了
Abell, you're on point.
埃贝 你说对了
Copy.
收到
Bishop,
主教
you're left.
你去左边
Copy.
收到
What's the rest of our air support?
我们其他的空中支援有什么？
Hornet's on standby. Thirty mikes out.
大黄蜂在待命 30公里以外
What do you want me to do?
你想让我做什么？
Nothing.
没什么
I got nothing on my end.
我这边一无所获
Same here.
我这也一样
Looks clear.
看起来很安全
Wait.
等等
Wait, I've got movement.
等等 我这有动静
Ten meters.
十米远
Oh, for fuck's sake.
哦 看在上帝的份上
It's a fucking oink oink.
这是一头他妈的 "嘤嘤"
What the hell's an oink oink?
什么是 "嘤嘤"？
A fucking pig, dumbass.
一头他妈的猪，蠢货
Pretty sure you got a picture of her in your wallet.
你钱包里肯定有她的照片
Fucker.
混蛋
This is serious bad guy lair shit.
这是大坏蛋的老巢
Got two tangos on the bridge.
桥上有两个哨兵
A third on the far right.
第三个在右边远处
Other side of the tent.
帐篷的另一边
See a Starbucks down there?
看到星巴克了吗？
I see number four on the lower part of the S-bend road
我看到四号位于 S 弯的下方
Let's push down.
往下压
Okay. Clear.
好了 没问题
Clear.
安全
Okay. We're gonna call this OP1. Air Force,
好 我们叫这里为OP1 空管员
set up up top.
联络空中做好设置
Abell, you stay put. Set up your hindsight.
埃贝 你别动 设置好你的瞄准镜
Bishop, you're with me.
主教 你和我在一起
We're gonna wrap around southeast 100 meters.
我们要绕到东南方100米处
Hooah.
呼啊
You good?
你好了吗？
Yeah, I think so.
好了 我想是的
Okay. Go forth and conquer.
好的 去放手干吧
All right, gents.
好了 队员们
Sit tight.
守好
Call out what you see.
看到什么就报告
I want a head count on that compound before we move on it.
在开始行动之前 我要先点清那院子里的人数
Sug?
糖？
When can we get a nice gig in Hawaii?
我们什么时候能去夏威夷搞个漂亮的演出？
Sick of swamp crotch.
讨厌裤裆湿漉漉的
I don't think they'd allow you back in Hawaii since last time.
我想自从上次之后 他们不会再让你回夏威夷了
That was one time.
就那么一次
Piece of shit. Fucking.
一坨屎 他妈的
Got movement.
有动静
All right, this sure looks like our guy.
好吧 这看起来很像我们要找的人
Bishop, can you confirm?
主教 你能确认吗？
Yeah, that's Petrov all right.
没错 那就是彼得罗夫没错
Okay,
好吧
if he's here,
如果他在这里
the asset's gotta be close.
目标一定在附近
Thunderbolt Squadron?
雷电中队？
No, it's not.
不 不是
I'm sorry I can't do that for you.
很抱歉 我不能为你做这些
You're gonna have to call the operator back.
你得回头去找接线员
If you ask for extension 141, that's Thunderbolt. Uh-huh.
你要 141 号分机 那才是雷电中队 嗯哼
Yeah, no problem.
没问题
Guys...
伙计们...
what the fuck?
搞什么鬼？
What's the problem, Captain?
有什么问题吗 上尉？
I asked you to keep an ear on this phone.
我让你们注意点这个电话
Some smartass turned the goddamn ringer off.
有个机灵鬼把该死的铃声关了
Why don't you turn it back on?
你为什么不把它打开？
I have
我打开了
Is your wife actually in labor, Captain?
你妻子真的要生了吗 队长
On the precipice, sir.
随时可能生产 长官
Water's broken?
羊水破了？
Impending.
快了
Having any of those, uh,
有任何这些 呃
contractions?
宫缩迹象吗？
Well, since you asked,
既然你
right now,
现在
40 mics apart.
在 40 公里之外问起来了
Last night, she was tooting like
昨晚 她嚎得就像
a bugler at a Gettysburg reenactment.
葛底斯堡战役再现中的一名号兵
Currently, her cervix is
目前 她的子宫颈
two centimeters dilated and starting to yawn.
扩张了两厘米 可以打哈欠了
All right, that is too much information.
好吧 信息量太大了
Yes, it is, sir.
是的 长官
Airmen, for the love of God, make sure that phone's turned on.
飞手们 看在上帝的份上 确保那电话开着机
Thank you.
谢谢
Contact.
发现敌人
Multiple vehicles inbound. Eleven o'clock.
多辆车进站 11点钟方向
Oh, Petrov is on the move.
哦 彼得罗夫开始行动了
Who the hell are these guys?
这些家伙到底是谁？
Identify yourselves!
表明你们的身份！
Don't know.
不知道
Local militia?
当地民兵？
Kinda looks like Abu Sayyaf.
有点像阿布沙耶夫
Bishop, can you confirm?
主教 你能确认吗？
Yeah, I can't tell.
是啊 我也说不清楚
More guys with guns.
多了很多扛着枪的
Sure as shit ain't taking this compound 'til they leave.
在他们离开之前 是肯定没法把这院子拿下了
Check out the dude getting out the left side of the lead vehicle.
看看那个从领头车左侧下车的家伙
Tell me that doesn't look like Saeed Hashimi.
告诉我那看起来不像赛义德·哈希米
Fuck.
妈的
Who's that?
那是谁？
Head of Abu Sayyaf.
阿布沙耶夫组织的头子
Sure he's here to buy guns.
他肯定是来买枪的
Keep your eyes open.
保持观察
Guns on safety.
枪支上好保险
JTAC, what's the status of our air?
空管员 我们的空中情况如何？
Reaper still down, Hornet on standby.
死神仍然不在 大黄蜂在待命
You want it airborne?
你想让它升空？
Negative.
否定
Sit tight. Let me work on a new game plan.
守好 我来制定一个新的任务计划
Yo,
哟
drone's fixed.
无人机已修好
Handover in five.
五分钟后交接
I'm ready.
我准备好了
Fuck.
妈的
Playboy,
花花公子
this is Reaper 1-0, back on station. Checking in.
这里是死神10号 已归位 报到
Requesting permission to establish overhead
请求允许设立上空链接
Copy that. Good to have you back, Reaper.
收到 很高兴你回来了 死神
Grid is as follows,
坐标如下
November, Victor, 1-1-4-8-7-6-3-5. Over.
N V 1-1-4-8-7-6-3-5 结束
Copy grid, Playboy.
收到坐标 花花公子
I have contact.
我有发现
Open circular compound, one large concrete structure,
开放式圆形院落 一个大型混凝土结构
and a road heading north crossing a dam.
和一条向北穿越水坝的道路
Confirm target area.
确认目标区域
Roger that, you have target area in sight.
收到 目标区域就在眼前
I didn't know Hashimi was in bed with Petrov.
我不知道哈希米和彼得罗夫有一腿
Oh, Hashimi's a terrorist.
哦 哈希米是个恐怖分子
He's got to buy his guns from somewhere
他总得从某处买枪
Come.
来吧
Come here.
过来
The miss doesn't look too thrilled about it.
小姐看起来并不高兴
Yeah, this guy's definitely a creeper.
是啊 这家伙绝对是个变态
She's getting stranger danger vibes for sure.
她肯定感觉到了这个陌生人有危险
Hashimi and Petrov sitting in a tree
哈希米和彼得罗夫坐在树上
K-I-S-S...
亲亲...
Fuck.
妈的
Go away!
走
Run! Run, run, run.
快跑！快跑！快跑
Oh, fuck.
妈的
Take him!
带他走
Run!
跑！
What the fuck, Sugar? What are we doing?
搞什么 甜心？我们要干什么？
Warhawk, this is Alpha 1.
战鹰 这是阿尔法 1 号
Have hostiles engaging with civilians. Requesting updated ROE, over.
发现敌人与平民交火 要求更新作战规则 结束
Make him see.
让他明白
Allahu Akbar!
真主至大！
Fuck me.
我操
Oh fuck...
我操...
Motherfucker!
狗娘养的
Jesus Christ!
耶稣上帝啊
Petrov,
彼得罗夫
Papa!
爸爸
Fuck this, Sugar, I ain't watching this asshole lob off the kid's head.
去他妈的 甜心 我才不要看着这混蛋把那孩子的头砍下来
Papa!
爸爸
Kinney, stand by for potential diversion.
金尼 准备好转变计划
Reaper, we need weapons effects between the compound and the tent. Over.
死神 我们需要炸弹攻击大院和帐篷之间 完毕
Reaper 1-0. One by hellfire missile, copied.
死神 1-0  一枚地狱火导弹 收到
Papa!
爸爸
Abell, Bishop, you got a shot, you take it. Kinney, drop that fucking bomb.
埃贝 主教 你们有机会就开枪 金尼 扔下那该死的炸弹
Reaper, you are cleared hot! Say again, you are cleared hot!
死神 你立即发射 再说一遍 你立即发射
Copied.
收到
Target acquired.
目标已瞄准
Weapon's away. Impact 30 seconds.
武器已发射 30 秒后爆炸
No! Papa!
不 爸爸
Don't have thirty.
等不了三十秒
Run!
跑！
Run, kid. Run!
快跑 孩子快跑
Guys?
伙计们？
It's a fucking cave entrance.
这是个该死的洞穴入口
Kinney, you've got hostiles directly below you. Do not move. Do not even breathe.
金尼 你正下方有敌人 别动 不要大喘气
Abell, Bishop,
埃贝 主教
I need sights on targets.
我需要人盯住目标
Abell, you taking center. Bishop, extreme left. I'm on extreme right.
埃贝 你搞定中间那个 主教 最左边那个 我搞定最右边的
On one...
数到一...
In position.
就位
On one.
数到一
Three
三
two,
二
one,
一
Kinney!
金尼
Fuck!
妈的
Shit. Abell, you've got five hostiles on your six. Fifty meters.
妈的 埃贝 你背后有五个敌人 距离50米
Bishop, move. On me!
主教 快走 我掩护
All right, Abell.
好的 埃贝
Kinney, I need...
金尼 我需要...
Stay still, asshole.
别动 混蛋
A little help here, fellas!
帮个忙吧 伙计们！
Trying, buddy.
正在努力 伙计
Kinney, I need you to lay down some cover fire for Abell.
金尼 我需要你为埃贝提供火力掩护
Sug...
糖...
Yeah.
是啊
We got a situation.
有情况了
No shit.
不是吧
We got another situation. RPG twelve o'clock. Incoming!
又有情况了 RPG 正前方 来了
Motherfucker!
狗娘养的
I got you, man. I got you.
我来了 伙计 我来了
Okay.
好的
You're good, man.
你没事的 伙计
No, you're good, man. You're good. You're good. I got you.
不 你很好 伙计 没事的 有我在
Where's the med kit?
医药箱在哪里？
I'm gonna get you fixed up.
我会把你治好的
Come on, man. Where's the med kit?
来吧 伙计 医药箱在哪儿？
Kinney.
金尼
Abell, Abell. No, no, no.
埃贝 不 不
Fuck, fuck. Oh, fuck!
妈的 妈的
Abell is down. Abell is down.
埃贝倒下了 埃贝倒下了
Hello?
喂？
Oh, fuck.
妈的
Oh, fuck. Alpha 1, this Playboy.
妈的 阿尔法1号 这是花花公子
Kinney,
金尼
listen to me.
听我说
We are taking heavy fire from two two-man RPG teams.
我们正遭到两个双人火箭筒小组的猛烈攻击
I need some bombs down there now!
我现在需要一些炸弹
Wait, wh-what about Abell?
等等 埃贝怎么办？
Abell is dead.
埃贝死了
He's dead. I need you to stay focused, Sergeant. Get yourself together.
他死了 我需要你集中精力 中士 振作起来
Oh, fuck.
妈的
Reaper, we're taking RPG fire on the southeast side of the compound.
死神 我们遭到来自大院东南侧的火箭弹袭击
Two hundred meters south of my position.
在我位置的南边两百米处
Give me the biggest thing you got. Cleared hot.
给我你最厉害的火力 马上
Copy that, Playboy. We have eyes on the target.
收到 花花公子 我们已经看到目标了
1 by Blu 118.
一枚118燃烧弹
Weapons away.
炸弹已发射
Impact 20 seconds.
Where's that bomb, Sergeant?
炸弹在哪里 中士？
Twenty seconds!
RPG incoming!
RPG 来袭！
Fuck! Sugar?
妈的 甜心？
Sugar? Bishop!
甜心？主教
Oh, shit.
哦 该死
Fuck!
妈的
You got eyes on him?
你看到他了吗？
Lost him in the smoke.
在烟雾中失去了踪影
Fuck.
妈的
Did he pop the smoke?
他把烟掐灭了吗？
I don't know.
我不知道
Playboy, do you copy?
花花公子 收到了吗？
I see him.
我看到他了
Stay with him.
盯着他
Reaper? Reaper, you there?
死神？死神 你在吗？
Reaper?
死神？
Reaper, you there?
死神 你在吗？
We're here, Playboy.
我们在 花花公子
Give me the status of your team.
告诉我你们队伍的情况
Uh,
呃.....
KIA.
阵亡.
Okay, Playboy, let's do this by the numbers.
好吧 花花公子 让我们用数字来解决
Confirm your current grid location.
确认当前坐标位置
Yeah.
好
Uh,
呃.....
I'm headed northeast. November, Romeo, 2-7-6-0-niner-3-2-2.
我要去东北方向 N R 2-7-6-0-9-3-2-2
I'm, uh...
我...
I'm approx five clicks from the evac point.
我离撤离点大约5公里
I need you to scan forward 500 meters and make sure the area is clear.
我需要你扫描前方 500 米 确保该区域安全
Copy, Playboy. We got you.
收到 花花公子 我们掩护你
Scanning forward 500 meters. Standby.
扫描前方 500 米 准备
Yeah, area's clear.
是的 区域很安全
Area looks clear. You're good to move.
区域看起来安全 你可以行动了
Playboy, do you copy?
花花公子 收到了吗？
Playboy?
花花公子？
What's he doing? Is he moving?
他在做什么？他动了吗？
He's freaking out.
他吓坏了
You gotta calm him down.
你得让他冷静下来
Hey, Playboy. Good news.
嘿 花花公子 好消息
Helicopter is inbound to the evac point. The cavalry is on the way.
直升机正前往撤离点 援兵正在路上
You gotta get your ass on the move, son.
你得赶紧走了 孩子
You got to move, man. Let's go.
你得走了 伙计 我们走
Come on, soldier.
来吧 士兵
Get up and go.
站起来 走
Here we go. All right.
开始了 好了
You scan forward. I've got him.
你扫描前面 我看着他
Scanning forward.
向前扫描
Tell me what you see.
告诉我你看到了什么
距离着陆区5公里
Reaper,
死神
I think I'm hearing a truck.
我好像听到了卡车的声音
He's right.
他是对的
I have contact from the west.
我在西面有发现
Truck on the road, half a click.
卡车在路上 半公里外
I have contact from the east.
我在东面也有发现
Looks like they're converging on Playboy's position.
看起来他们正在向花花公子的位置靠拢
Playboy, be aware. You have converging targets east and west.
花花公子 注意 有目标向你东西两侧交汇
How much ordinance do you have left?
你还剩下多少火力？
One by hellfire. Air to ground 114. Standing by.
一枚地狱火 114空对地. 待命
You want those hornets airborne?
你想让那些大黄蜂升空吗？
Negative.
否定
Okay, Playboy, Tally. Eyes on target. What you want to do?
好了 花花公子 塔利 瞄准目标 你想做什么？
Keep eyes on it.
盯着它
Roger that. Standing by.
收到 随时待命
Reaper, do you have eyes on hostiles?
死神 你能看到敌人吗？
Confirmed hostiles from the east are armed.
确认来自东面的敌人持有武器
Are they Abu Sayyaf?
他们是阿布沙耶夫的人吗？
They've got weapons. Safe to assume.
他们有武器 八九不离十
Playboy, you copy?
花花公子 收到吗？
Can't talk right now.
现在不能说
Ah, for fuck's sake. Playboy, Playboy.
啊 他妈的 花花公子
Canine coming your way.
犬类朝你走去
You gotta be shitting me.
你在耍我吧
Fuck, Playboy.
操 花花公子
Buffalo Bill has dismounted. He is approaching your position.
水牛比尔下马了 他正在走近你的位置
Looks like he's coming towards Lassie.
他好像朝莱西走过来了
Do not move.
不要动
Playboy,
花花公子
Buffalo Bill is above your position. Do not move.
水牛比尔在你的位置上方 不要移动
Okay, Playboy. Looks like Lassie's going home.
好了 花花公子 看来莱西要回家了
Buffalo Bill has remounted.
水牛比尔重新上马
Hostiles are leaving the party. Stand by.
敌人正在离开派对 待命
Goddammit.
该死的
Playboy,
花花公子
Buffalo Bill and his buddy are gone. The truck is gone.
水牛比尔和他的伙伴不见了 卡车也不见了
You are clear tracking 500 meters to your north.
你到北面 500 米之间都很安全
There's a path up that ridge on your one o'clock.
你一点钟方向的山脊上有条小路
距离着陆区 1.2 公里
Hey, Playboy,
嘿 花花公子
how you holding up?
你还好吗？
I'm all right.
我没事
Where are you from, man?
你是哪里人 伙计？
Ohio.
俄亥俄州
No shit.
不是吧
Me, too.
我也是
Brook Park.
布鲁克公园
Middleburg Heights.
米德尔堡高地
We're basically fucking neighbors.
我们基本上就是他妈的邻居
O-H.
俄-亥
I-O.
亥-俄
Fellow Buckeye.
俄亥俄老乡
Get home much?
回家多吗？
Yeah.
是啊
Yeah, I was just there.
是的 我刚回去过
Had to bury my father.
得去埋葬我的父亲
Oh, man. Sorry to hear.
哦 伙计 真遗憾
Yeah, it's okay.
是啊 没关系
Were you guys close?
你们关系好吗？
Yeah.
是啊
Yeah, he was a good guy.
是啊 他是个好人
In Sweet Sixteen news, the fucking Buckeyes
十六强新闻：该死的俄亥俄大学队
just shit the bed against VCU.
在对阵弗吉尼亚联邦大学队的比赛中一败涂地
First round.
第一轮
Trying to depress me more?
想让我更沮丧？
Sorry, man.
对不起 伙计
Hey, you ever got up to Mama Santas on Mayfield?
嘿 你去过梅菲尔德的妈妈桑塔斯餐厅吗？
Are you kidding me?
你在开玩笑吗？
I lived at that place during high school. Fucking great.
我高中时就住在那边 太他妈好吃了
I know, right? I met my first wife there in '95.
我知道 95 年 我在那里遇到了我的第一任妻子
Oh, yeah?
哦 是吗？
Yeah. We met in line.
是的 我们在排队时认识的
We both ordered stromboli.
我们俩都点了长方形炸肉卷
Who the fuck orders stromboli?
谁他妈会点炸肉卷？
I know, right?
我知道 对吧？
I thought it was meant to be.
我以为这是命中注定的
And it was.
的确如此
Right up until it wasn't,
直到它不是
you know?
你知道吗？
My current wife hates the shit.
我现在的妻子讨厌这玩意儿
She jealous?
她吃醋了？
Nah, man, worse...
不 伙计 更糟...
she's vegan.
她是素食主义者
Ah, man. That is worse.
啊 伙计 是更糟
How do you know if someone's a vegan?
怎么才能知道某人是不是素食主义者？
How?
怎么做？
They will tell you.
他们会告诉你的
You're getting really close now, man. Just keep up the pace. Good work.
你现在真的很接近了 伙计 保持节奏 干得好
ETA on the helo?
直升机的预计抵达时间？
Playboy 0-6, this is Blackbird 2-5,
花花公子 0-6 这是黑鸟 2-5
approaching LZ from east.
从东面接近着陆点
ETA three mikes, over.
预计到达时间三分钟 完毕
Copy.
收到
Reaper, how's my path to the LZ?
死神 我去着陆点的路线怎么样？
Clear.
安全
Path is clear.
路线安全
Time to get the hell out of dodge, Playboy.
是时候结束逃亡之旅了 花花公子
Thanks for the eyes, Reaper.
谢谢你的照应 死神
Happy to do it.
乐意之至
Hey, drop me a line next time you're in Vegas.
嘿 下次你来拉斯维加斯的时候给我来个电话
I have a solid hookup for Disney on Ice.
我在冰上迪士尼有可靠的关系
You lost me.
你把我搞糊涂了
I might pass on that,
我可能会放弃那个
but I'm at Nellis all the time.
但我一直都在内利斯
I'm here, man. Call CENTCOM.
我在这 呼叫中央司令部
Raven Squadron. Eddie Grim.
乌鸦中队 埃迪·格里姆
Just ask for Reaper.
找 "死神 "就行
Will do.
好的
Blackbird 2-5, I have a visual. LZ is clear for extract.
黑鸟2-5 我看到了 撤离区安全
Marking position with I-R.
用红外装置标记位置
Roger that, Playboy. I have your position marked.
收到 花花公子 我已经标记了你的位置
Contact! I'm hit! I'm hit!
交火！我被击中了
Playboy, are you injured?
花花公子 你受伤了吗？
Negative!
否定
Must have hit my plate.
一定是打中我的防弹衣了
Reaper, hostiles, 100 meters east. Two hundred meters south.
死神 敌军 东边100米 南200米
Contact! Blackbird. I have multiple targets around the LZ.
交火 黑鸟 我在降落区周围发现多个目标
Contact, Blackbird. Three more hostiles on the west ridge
交火 黑鸟 西面山脊上还有三个敌人
Small arms and an RPG.
小武器和火箭弹
Better move your ass.
你最好快点走
RPG!
火箭弹
Shit!
妈的
Blackbird, can you stay in the area until we can find a secure LZ?
黑鸟 在我们找到安全降落区之前 你能待在这个区域吗？
Negative, Playboy. LZ is too hot.
不行 花花公子 着陆区太危险了
Back to you as fast as we can.
我们会尽快回来找你
Shit!
妈的
Reaper, west ridge.
死神 西面山脊
Contact, Playboy.
有敌人 花花公子
Three more trucks right through.
又有三辆卡车前来
Reaper, need the bomb 300 meters to the west.
死神 需要轰炸西面 300 米处
Cleared hot!
立即发射
Roger that, Playboy.
收到 花花公子
Tally. Eyes on target.
统计 瞄准目标
Stay where you are, assholes.
站着别动 混蛋们
Standby, Hellfire is firing on my order.
准备 地狱火正在按我的指令发射
Weapon away. Impact 20 seconds.
武器已发射 20 秒后起效
Target is down. Now get the fuck out of there.
目标已解决 现在赶紧离开
Fuck! Taking fire.
妈的 被火力压制
This ain't done.
这还没完
Got another truck coming in from the west.
又有一辆卡车从西面开过来了
Jesus Christ, I'm pinned down.
天哪 我被压制住了
How are they seeing me?
他们怎么看到我的？
It's his strobe!
是他的红外装置
They must have night vision. He's gotta turn his strobe off.
他们一定有夜视仪 他得把红外装置关掉
It's your strobe, Playboy. Turn off your strobe.
是你的红外装置 花花公子 关掉你的红外装置
Taking fire from the east. Drop everything you have.
正遭受来自东面的袭击 扔下你全部的火药
Playboy, I am Winchester. I'm out of bombs.
花花公子 我没弹药了 我没有炸弹了
ETA on the hornets is two mikes.
大黄蜂的预计到达时间是两分钟
Playboy... this is Hornet 1.
花花公子....这是大黄蜂1号
Entering point out level.
入场点外围
I'm coming in on an east west heading.
我从东西方向过来
Roger that, Hornet 1.
收到 大黄蜂 1 号
I'm 200 meters north of target grid.
我在目标坐标以北 200 米处
Keep all fire south of target grid.
所有火力保持在目标坐标以南
I say again, all fire south.
我再说一遍 所有火力往南
Copy that. Be advised this will be danger close.
收到 请注意 这将是一次危险的亲密接触
Yes, yes. Cleared hot.
是的 是的 立刻发射
Copy.
收到
Three, two, one!
三 二 一
Shit!
妈的
Still taking fire from west!
仍在遭受来自西面的火力袭击！
Copy, Playboy. Coming around for another run.
收到 花花公子 正在前往再来一轮
Fuck!
妈的
Fuck this!
去他妈的
What do you want, Airman?
你要干吗 飞手？
- Yeah, I'm doing a Starbucks run. - Moving!
- 是的 我正在做星巴克跑 - 移动
Colonel Packett is springing.
帕克特上校正在弹跳
A what?
什么？
Starbucks.
星巴克
Have you lost your mind?
你疯了吗？
Airman, leave!
飞手 请离开
Eyes on that hornet.
盯着那只大黄蜂
Give me some fire on the west ridge.
给我西边的山脊上来点火力
You're cleared hot.
立即发射
Confirm. West or east?
确认 西边还是东边？
West! West!
西边 西边
Copy that. This one is going to be danger close.
收到 这一次会非常危险
We still do not have visual on you.
我们仍然没有看见你的位置
It's fine. Just drop it! You're cleared hot!
没事的 发射吧 立即发射
Be advised, this is danger close.
请注意 这会非常危险
Altitude.
海拔过低
Pull up.
拉升
Playboy, I am Winchester.
花花公子 我没弹药了
Hornet 1 is RTB.
大黄蜂 1 号返回基地
Copy that.
收到
Good shooting.
打的不错
How's it looking, Reaper?
怎么样 死神？
Playboy, from what we can see, it looks clear.
花花公子 从我们看到的情况来看 似乎很安全
These fuckers know we're out there now, so...
这些混蛋知道我们在外面 所以...
do not discount any surprises.
不要忽视任何意外惊喜
We got another LZ?
我们还有另一个着陆区吗？
There's a clearing
有一块空地
two clicks northeast of your position.
在你所在位置的东北方向两公里
You're not gonna like it though.
不过你不会喜欢的
You say northeast?
你是说东北方向？
A-firm, Playboy.
确定 花花公子
Northeast is up a big fucking hill.
东北方向是一座该死的大山
I know, man. I told you, you weren't gonna like it.
我知道 我告诉过你 你不会喜欢的
I'm sorry, but that is the closest LZ option we have.
很抱歉 但这是我们能选择的最近的着陆区了
Playboy, the helo is airborne.
花花公子 直升机已经升空了
ETA to the alternate LZ is 90 mikes.
到达备用着陆区的预计时间为 90 分钟
You copy?
收到吗？
Yeah, I'm here.
是的 我在这里
How you doing, man?
你好吗？
Pretty gassed.
累死了
Yeah, no doubt.
是的 毫无疑问
Hang in there, okay?
坚持住 好吗？
Sorry about the failed evac, man.
很抱歉撤离失败 伙计
Now you know.
现在你知道了
Don't trust Air Force Captains. Traditionally, we are full of shit.
不要相信空军上尉 我们经常搞得一蹋糊涂
Captain?
上尉？
Yeah.
是啊
You said you met your first wife in '95.
你说你在 95 年遇到了你的第一任妻子
Yeah, I am old as shit. I should be a general by now.
是啊 我已经老得不成样子了 我现在早应该当上将军了
I got three ex-wives. I got eight kids. I got a new wife. I got a new kid on the way.
我有三个前妻 八个孩子 一个新妻子 和一个即将出生的孩子
I need the active duty bonuses.
我需要现役奖金
If I go out from Captain, they'll make me an instructor, so fuck that.
如果我从上尉转业 他们会让我当教官 所以去他妈的吧
You fly fixed wings before the birds?
你在此之前先飞的固定翼？
That is a very long story, my friend.
说来话长 我的朋友
But, yes, originally, I did sign up to be a pilot.
不过 是的 最初我确实是报名当飞行员的
But apparently, the Air Force thought
但显然 空军认为
my responses to authority were not normal.
我对权威的反应不太正常
So that goat got fucked.
所以那只山羊被干了
Subtle.
经典
What happened?
怎么了？
Well, I shot my big mouth off,
好吧 我闭上大嘴巴之后
and I found myself reassigned to USAF-SF
发现自己被重新分配到美国空军安全部队
guarding shit in the middle of nowhere for 20 years.
在荒郊野外看守了 20 年狗屎
Eareckson Base in the Aleutian, Pine Gap in Australia...
阿留申群岛的埃雷克森基地 澳大利亚的松树峡....
Playboy, do you copy?
花花公子 收到了吗？
Yeah. Yeah, I'm here.
对 我在
What happened?
怎么了？
Slid halfway down a fucking mountain.
从半山腰滑下来
Oh, fuck, man. You okay?
哦 他妈的 伙计 你还好吗？
You hurt?
你受伤了吗？
Yeah. Just my pride.
是啊 心碎了一地
Uh, Reaper, I've got movement in front of Playboy.
呃 死神 花花公子前面有动静了
One hundred meters northwest.
西北方向 100 米处
Zoom in.
放大
Three armed hostiles.
三名武装分子
Playboy, you have three hostiles heading your way.
花花公子 有三个敌人朝你来了
Find cover.
找个掩护
Fuck.
妈的
Shit.
Scan forward. Keep me with him.
向前扫描 让我跟着他
Copy.
收到
Got him?
看到他了吗？
I'm looking. I'm looking.
我在找 我在找
Fuck.
妈的
I got him
我找到他了
He's heading downstream.
他往下游去了
God fucking dammit!
真他妈该死
Get me the colonel.
给我接上校
Yeah.
是啊
Keep looking.
继续找
I lost him under the canopy.
我在瀑布下跟丢了他
Fuck.
妈的
Reaper, what's the sitrep?
死神 情况如何？
This mission has gone to shit, Colonel.
这次任务搞砸了 上校
I got an op who's been taken.
我有个特工被抓了
We are 12 hours in.
我们已经进行了 12 个小时
I'm Winchester, but we cannot leave the target area
我没有火力了 但我们不能离开目标区域
because we have the only eyes.
因为我们是唯一的眼睛
Requesting permission to stay in the chair until we get the soldier home.
请求允许我一直坐在这里 直到我们把士兵送回家
How you feeling? Are you feeling sharp?
感觉如何？感觉还敏锐吗？
Oh yeah.
哦 是的
Sharp as an elephant's ass.
像大象屁股一样敏锐
Staff Sergeant?
上士？
I'm good, sir.
我很好 长官
Okay, Eddie. Stay in the chair.
好吧 埃迪 呆在椅子上
Get it done, you two.
搞定它 你们两个
Fuck you.
去你妈的
Come on, Playboy.
来吧 花花公子
Come on. Talk to me.
说吧 跟我说话
Oh, shit.
哦 该死
You got him?
你发现他了？
It's all radio chatter about the JSOC asset.
无线电里都是关于联合特种行动小组人质的消息
Who?
谁？
The reason those guys are there,
这些队员去那边的原因
not confirmed,
还未确认
but one says Borneo, the other Yemen.
但一个说在婆罗洲 另一个说在也门
Yemen?
也门？
That's halfway around the fucking world. You shitting me?
那可是绕了半个地球啊 你在耍我吗？
Who's saying that?
谁说的？
Reading between the lines with CIA or DIA.
从字里行间看来像是中情局或国防情报局
Man.
天
Alphabet soup motherfuckers!
他妈的字母派
You can't trust a word they say.
他们说的话一个字都不能信
Hands!
举手
Are you injured?
你受伤了吗？
Look at me.
看着我
I thought you were dead.
我以为你死了
Here.
给你
Drink this. Drink. Drink. Drink.
喝了这个 喝吧 喝吧
Here. Put that on, okay?
给你 穿上 好吗？
Okay?
好吗？
An RPG exploded on your position.
一枚火箭弹在你的位置上爆炸了
Near,
附近
not on.
没炸上
Listen.
听着
Bishop got captured.
主教被抓了
He's injured pretty bad.
他伤得很重
I gotta go.
我得走了
We gotta go back and get him.
我们得回去救他
So,
所以
grab what you can, okay? Here.
能拿多少拿多少 好吗？给你
Take this. Here.
拿着这个 拿着
Put them in here. Put them in here.
放在这里 放在这里
Here, take this.
给 拿上这个
Come on.
来吧
You following me, Sergeant?
你在跟踪我吗 中士？
Hey. Look,
嘿 看
I get it.
我明白
This is not where you want to be,
你也不想在这里
but you got to dig, okay?
但你必须加油 好吗？
It's not here. It's not here. It's here.
不是这 不是这 是这里
Bishop's in trouble.
主教有麻烦了
We gotta go back and get him.
我们得回去救他
Okay.
好的
You can still shoot, can't you?
你还能开枪吧？
Yeah.
是啊
Let's go.
我们走吧
Still have your battery?
电池还在吗？
No, I lost it in the fall.
不 失陷时丢了
Let me see your knife.
让我看看你的刀
What for?
干吗？
I'm gonna call Warhawk.
我要呼叫战鹰
With a water bottle?
用水瓶？
Come on, you piece of shit.
来吧 你这坨屎
Reaper, this is Playboy
死神 这里是花花公子
Playboy, where the fuck are you?
花花公子 你他妈的在哪里？
I'm with Alpha one.
我和阿尔法一号在一起
We're headed back to the initial AO.
我们要回到最初的作战区域
No, no, no, no. Negative. Negative, Playboy.
不 不 不行 不行 花花公子
We have Intel the asset has been found.
情报显示 人质已经找到
We're not going for the asset.
我们不是为了人质
Say again?
再说一遍？
We're not going for the asset.
我们不是去抢人质
One of our team members was captured. We're going in to get him.
我们的一名队员被抓了 我们要去救他
Playboy, a QRF is being assembled. Hold your position until they're deployed.
花花公子 快速反应部队正在集结 坚守阵地 等他们部署完毕
Negative, Reaper. There's no time.
不行 死神 没时间了
Get on the horn with CJSOTF, and let them know our sitrep.
与联合特种作战司令部联系  向他们报告我们的战场态势
We're gonna need planes on standby. ETA to target area is 6-0 mikes.
我们需要飞机待命 到达目标区域的预计时间是60分
We'll confirm grid then. Over.
届时我们将确认坐标 完毕
What direction you heading, Playboy?
你要往哪个方向 花花公子？
Give me your bearing...
给我你的坐标
Playboy?
花花公子？
Lost comms.
失去通讯
Fuck!
妈的
Connect me to CJSOTF.
将我连接到联合特种作战司令部
Well, I know it's unusual, Eileen. Just fucking connect me, okay?
好吧 我知道这是不寻常的 艾琳 就他妈给我接通 好吗？
So where is he?
他在哪里？
No idea.
不知道
What's the plan?
有什么计划？
Drop some bombs, create a diversion,
投掷炸弹 声东击西
go in and get him.
进去找到他
Kill anyone that gets in our way.
杀光所有妨碍我们的人
Where do you want the bombs?
你想把炸弹投在哪里？
You're the JTAC. You tell me.
你是空管员 你来告诉我
Probably the best place would be along those cave entrances on this ridge line.
最佳地点可能是沿着山脊线上的洞穴入口
Space them out 15 minutes apart while we go in.
等我们进去 间隔 15 分钟之后 把他们轰出来
Sound good?
听起来不错吧？
Sounds good.
听起来不错
Find Bishop, make our move when the first strike hits.
找到主教 在第一波攻击到来时采取行动
Second strike should hold their attention.
第二波应该能吸引他们的注意力
And the last one?
最后一波呢？
Mass effect.
质量效应
Let's turn those caves inside out.
让我们把这些洞穴掀个底朝天
Fuckin' A, kid.
好极了 小子
Fuckin' A.
好极了
Yeah, I'm here. What do you got?
是的 我在 有什么装备？
B1 full payload? That will do the job.
B1 满载？这就够了
I will confirm
我会在
the 9 line with Bone 0-1 when received.
Roger.
收到
B1 in the air, Colonel.
B1升空 上校
Copy that. Nice work.
收到 干得好
Reaper, this is Playboy.
死神 这里是花花公子
Copy, Playboy. I'm here.
收到 花花公子 我在
Okay. Game plan is to use CAS to strike a set of cave structures
好的 游戏计划是使用 CAS 打击大院背面的
to the north of the compound as a diversion.
一组洞穴 作为幌子
I need three attacks spaced approx 15 mikes apart starting at 1100.
我需要三次攻击 从 11 点开始 每次间隔约 15 分钟
Eleven hundred. Mark that.
First strike, 1100.
第一波打击 11点
Intent for first two attacks is to hold their attention.
前两波攻击的目的是吸引他们的注意力
Final attack should have enough ordnance to neutralize all enemy in the caves.
最后一波攻击应该有足够的弹药来消灭洞穴中的所有敌人
Type three BOC.
打出三波作战任务
November, Victor, 1-1-4-8-7-6-3-5.
N V 1-1-4-8-7-6-3-5
Say again, Playboy. Say again.
再说一遍 花花公子 再说一遍
November, Victor, 1-1-4-8-7-6-3-5. Over.
N V 1-1-4-8-7-6-3-5 结束
Copy.
收到
Eyes on you.
看到你了
Three strikes. Eleven hundred. Diversion.
三次攻击 11点 转移注意力
Eleven fifteen, diversion.
Eleven thirty, we're gonna light that
shit up and blow it to fuck.
Confirm, Playboy.
确认 花花公子
Oh, fuck.
妈的
Battery's dead.
电池没电了
We good?
可以了吗？
Hope so.
希望如此
Playboy, confirm?
花花公子 确认吗？
Lost comms.
失去通讯
Fuck.
妈的
All right, we all know the plan.
好了 我们都知道计划了
You both did some fine work here today. Get out of here.
你们俩今天都干得不错 出去吧
No, no, no, no, no.
不 不 不
We are not going anywhere.
我们哪儿也不去
I wasn't asking. You're done.
我不是在问你  你结束了
You're ten hours over your eight-hour shift.
你的八小时轮班已经超了十小时了
Okay, Reaper. Out of the chair.
好了 死神 离开椅子
Eat a bag of dicks, Hawkins.
吃屎去吧 霍金斯
Hawkins?
霍金斯？
It's Andrews.
是安德鲁斯
Come on. Let me get you up.
来吧 我扶你起来
No.
不
Exit the chair, Reaper.
离开椅子 死神
There's no fucking way I'm off this op.
我他妈不可能退出这次行动的
No fucking way.
不可能
I got one KIA.
我有一人阵亡
One MIA.
一人失踪
And I got two fucking nut jobs
还有两个该死的疯子
trying to take on an entire Abu Sayyaf camp.
试图攻打整个阿布沙耶夫基地
That leaves one team, i.e. us,
这样就只剩下一支队伍 也就是我们
to make sure this whole thing doesn't go to hell in a fucking handbasket.
来确保这整件事不会一发不可收拾
You finished?
你说完了吗？
I'm not finished.
我还没说完
I can keep going.
我可以继续
Then I suggest you think very carefully
那么我建议你仔细考虑一下
about the next words that come out of your mouth, Captain.
你的下一句话 上尉
Oh, come on, Virgil. You're gonna pull rank on me?
哦 来吧 维吉尔 你要对我发号施令吗？
You told me I could have this chair
你说过我可以坐在这里
until the op was done.
直到行动结束
Go and watch the basketball.
去看篮球吧
Sir, with all due respect, this is Reaper's op. We should be allowed to...
长官 恕我直言 这是死神的行动 我们应该被允许...
I don't recall asking your opinion, Staff Sergeant.
我不记得我问过你的意见 上士
Well, maybe that's your problem, Colonel.
也许这就是你的问题所在 上校
I would strongly advise you to not go down the same rabbit hole
我强烈建议你不要和你这里的同伴
as your partner here.
走上同样的歪路
She did not say a word, Colonel.
她一句话也没说 上校
Not a single word.
一个字也没说
Exit the chair.
离开椅子
Exit the room,
离开房间
and I will do my best to forget this conversation ever happened.
我会尽我所能忘记这次谈话
Don't fuck it up, Junior.
别搞砸了 小安迪
You got it.
你放心吧
First strike 1100. It's just a diversion.
第一波攻击 11点 只是个障眼法
Second strike 11...
第二波攻击 11...
Captain!
上尉
I'm good. I'm good.
我很好 我很好
You're dismissed.
你可以离开了
All right.
好吧
Eyes.
观察
One guy in the tent.
帐篷里有一个
Two guys on the balcony.
两个在阳台上
What's our time?
还有多少时间？
Twenty.
二十分
This is gonna get ugly.
情况会变得很糟
I need you focused. Head on a swivel.
我要你集中精力 前后多观察观察
If you see something I don't,
如果你看到了我没看到的
you say 'contact left, contact right.'
就说'左边遇敌 右边遇敌'
Somebody comes from behind us,
有人从我们身后过来
you say 'six.'
你就说'六'
I'll handle the rest.
剩下的交给我吧
Only shoot if it's necessary. We got to keep this quiet for as long as we can.
必要时才开枪 我们得尽可能保持安静
For what it's worth,
我想说的是
you earned your tier one status today.
你今天赢得了一线队员的资格
Does that mean I get paid more?
意味着我能加薪了？
Fuck no. It just sounds cooler.
才怪 就是听起来酷点
You ready?
准备好了吗？
Nope.
没有
You?
你？
Always.
时刻准备着
Let's do it.
开始吧
距 离 首 次 攻
击 时 间 还 剩
Okay.
好的
Fucker.
混蛋
You good?
你还好吗？
Yeah.
是啊
Alright.
好吧
He's jammed.
他被卡住了
Go, go, go, go!
快 快 快
Come on!
来吧
Gun right. Right!
右边有枪 右边
Move! Move!
走 走
On me.
跟着我
On you.
跟着你
Contact left!
左侧遇敌
Drop down!
下拉
You good?
你还好吗？
Fuck!
妈的
Fuck.
Oh, fuck!
妈的
Grenade!  Get down!
手雷 趴下
Hey, Sug.
嘿 糖
Bishop.
主教
This your idea of a rescue mission?
这就是你的救援计划？
I think I got them right where I want 'em.
我想我找到了我要找的地方
You look like ass.
你看起来糟透了
Hey,
嘿
how you doing, Bishop?
你好吗 主教？
Talk to me.
跟我说话
Ah...
啊...
Air Force,
空管员
I think
我认为
we're in a bad spot.
我们的处境很不妙
Yeah, we're in a bad spot.
是啊 我们的情况很不妙
Hey!
嘿！
Hey, yo!
嘿
Hey, listen to me, man.
嘿 听我说 伙计
They're gonna drop bombs on these caves. You understand?
他们会向这些洞里投掷炸弹 你听得懂吗？
Bombs on these caves.
炸了这些洞穴
If we don't get out of here, we're all gonna die.
如果我们不离开这里 我们都会死的
You understand? Bombs on these caves.
你听得懂吗？会轰炸这些洞穴
Fuck!
妈的
Stupid fucks!
蠢货
Boeing 0-1, this is Sunburn 0-6. We're tracking your position.
波音0-1 这里是晒伤0-6 我们正在追踪你的位置
Be advised ETA to first drone strike,
请注意第一次无人机袭击的预计时间
two mikes.
还有两分钟
All right, let's fucking rock and roll.
好了 让我们开始摇滚吧
Zoom out 400 meters.
放大到 400 米
I think they know
我想他们知道
I'm not gonna last much longer.
我坚持不了多久了
Just... just... just hang on a second, all right, man?
再 再坚持一会 好吗？
I'm gonna figure out how to get us out of here.
我会想办法把我们弄出去的
I'm already out.
我已经不行了
Just get Bishop and get yourselves out of here.
带上主教 你们离开这里吧
Okay?
好吗？
Nah, you're good, man. You're good, you're good.
不 你没事的 伙计 没事的
Don't...
别...
fucking touch him!
他妈的碰他！
Or I'll fucking fucking fuck!
否则我就他妈的他妈的
Fuck!
妈的
Fucking pieces of shit!
该死的废物
Come on!
来吧
Get your fucking hands off him!
把你的脏手从他身上拿开
Fucking coward.
该死的懦夫
Sugar?
甜心？
Get your fucking hands off him!
把你的脏手从他身上拿开
you like that?
你喜欢吗？
Sugar?
甜心？
Oh, fuck.
妈的
Sugar?
甜心？
I'm good.
我很好
Fuck!
妈的
Welcome to Guantanamo.
欢迎来到关塔那摩
Go.
去吧
距 离 第 二 次
攻 击 时 间 还 剩
You know Japan invaded these lands in 1941.
要知道 日本曾在 1941 年入侵过这些土地
Hm. Built these caves with the intent to stay
嗯 建造这些洞穴的目的是为了留下
but our Moro brothers defeated them very quickly. Hm.
但我们的摩洛兄弟很快就打败了他们 嗯
You know this dam they built...
你知道他们建的这个大坝...
it was a very forward step.
这是非常超前的一步
Was it this blood
是不是这些血
washed from the land
从土地上冲到了
and into our mouths?
我们的嘴里？
But not to me.
但对我来说不是
We answer to no one but ourselves.
我们只对自己负责
We were having a fairly pleasant day.
我们今天过得相当愉快
Blessed by the...
受到....
Then, how you say?
然后 怎么说？
Someone rains on our parade?
有人来捣乱？
Removed one imperialist...
赶走了一个帝国主义...
just to find another.
只是为了找到另一个
This is not the conversation we should be having right now.
这不是我们现在应该进行的对话
No?
不是吗？
What should we talk about?
我们应该谈些什么？
I told you.
我告诉过你
There's more bombs on the way.
还有更多炸弹要过来
Ah,
啊
I'm not interested in your faceless bombs.
我对你们这些不露脸的炸弹不感兴趣
You see, real results
你看 真正的成果
are created face-to-face,
是面对面创建的
interactions
互动
like what you and I are doing right here.
像你和我正在这里做的事
Where are the other commandos located?
其他突击队员在哪里？
There's no more. It's just us!
没有了 只有我们
Your jets are still in the area.
你们的飞机仍在该区域
Someone must be communicating with them.
一定有人在和他们联络
We were communicating with them.
就是我们与他们联络过
Listen,
听着
there's more strikes on the way.
还有更多的攻击正在路上
If we don't get out of here, we're all fucking dust.
如果我们不离开这里 我们都会变成灰烬
No! You are dust!
不！你才是灰烬！
Fucking dust!
该死的灰烬
How does this feel?
感觉如何？
To be this scared.
这么害怕
Too weak to do anything about your own death.
对自己的死亡无能为力
You may think that I do this
你可能认为我这样做
without feeling anything.
没有任何感觉
That is wrong.
这是不对的
To kill affects me.
杀人会影响我
To embrace the brutality of this affects me.
接受这种残酷会影响我
And that is the difference between you and I.
这就是你我之间的区别
I look a man in the eye,
我看着一个人的眼睛
and I make my choice intimate.
我亲手做出的选择
The bomb!
炸弹
Excuse me?
你说什么？
Sir?
先生？
I got this thing here I don't even know...
我这有个东西 我不知道...
I don't even know if this is something that exists.
我甚至不知道这东西是否存在
My wife's written it down, so she might have got it wrong.
是我妻子写的 所以她可能弄错了
It sounds a little crazy,
这听起来有点疯狂
but, uh,
但是
I gotta ask, you know?
我得问问
Do you have
你们是否有
artisanal tree nut fermented plant-based cashew
手工采摘树果发酵植物腰果
and tahini smoked vegan new cheese.
和塔希尼烟熏素食新奶酪
Is that a thing?
有这玩意吗？
Yeah,
是啊
right here.
就在这里
Man after my own heart.
我心目中的好男人
Huh. I would have bet money against that. Thank you very much.
哈？我本想在这上赌一把的 非常感谢
All right, let's fucking rock and roll.
好了 让我们开始摇滚吧
Zoom out 400 meters.
放大 400 米
It's fucking showtime.
好戏上场了
Ready to fire.
准备发射
Bombs away.
投弹
Six, five, four, three,
六 五 四 三
two, one.
二 一
Impact
爆炸
距离最后攻击的时间还剩
Holy shit.
我的妈呀
You JSOC?
你是联合特别行动小组的？
Can you walk?
你能走路吗？
Who are you?
你是谁？
I am a Cavalry.
我是个大兵
Hey!
嘿！
Fuck!
妈的
Fucking hell, Kinney.
他妈的 金尼
You good?
你还好吗？
Yeah, yeah.
是啊 是啊
Who the fuck's that guy?
那人他妈的是谁？
The asset...
人质...
I think.
我想是的
Come on. We gotta move.
快点 我们得走了
So soon?
这么快？
Let's go.
我们走
距离最后攻击的时间还剩
Which way?
怎么走？
I think it's this way. Let's keep moving.
我估计是这边 继续前进
Fuck.
妈的
Yeah.
是啊
Okay.
好的
All right.
Sit here for a second. I'll be right back.
在这儿坐一会儿 我马上回来
Boeing 0-1, this is Sunburn 0-6. You are inbound to target. Five mikes.
波音0-1 这里是晒伤0-6 你正锁定目标 五公里
Copy incoming. We're hot. Let me know when I can cross extend at 7-9-8-4-0.
收到 我们已就绪 告诉我什么时候能开火
Fuck,
妈的
fuck, fuck, fuck.
他妈的 他妈的 他妈的
Come on.
来吧
Fuck.
妈的
Barbeque creepy peanuts.
烧烤花生
Yeah!
是啊
Come on!
来吧
Vegan sour cream.
素食酸奶油
Come on! Yeah!
来吧
Plant based feta.
植物羊乳酪
Oh, you motherfucker!
你个混蛋
Fuck.
妈的
Come on, man. Come on.
快点 伙计 快点
Pick up the fucking phone.
快接电话 快接电话
Get the phone, Sergeant.
接电话  中士
Sergeant!
中士
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
Reaper. I need Reaper.
死神 我需要死神
Reaper's gone.
死神走了
Try his cell...
试试他的手机...
Wait, wait. Hold on.
等等 等等 别挂
702-166-42… 00.
Yeah! Come on!
是啊 来吧
Wait, wait, wait! Hold on!
等等 等等 别挂
Hello?
喂？
Fuck!
妈的
6-42 00.
Come on, man.
快点 伙计
I'm looking. I'm looking at all of the shelves. All right.
我在看 我所有的架子都看了 好的
Hey,
嘿
hold on.
等一下
No, I'm looking at...
不 我在看...
It was a number I didn't know.
是一个我不认识的号码
I'm looking at all the shelves,
我在看所有的货架
but they got real Mexican, you know?
但他们这有真的墨西哥货 你知道吗？
Cou... but with meat in it.
但里面有肉的
No, I'm not...
不 我没有...
Baby, okay.
宝贝 好的
All right? It's got meat in it.
好吗？里面有肉
Sorry I shouldn't have used the word real.
对不起 我不该用真的这个词
距离最后攻击的时间还剩
Sunburn 0-6, this is Boeing 0-1. Approaching target.
晒伤 0-6 这是波音 0-1 接近目标
Come on. Move! Move!
来吧 快走 快走
tampon because
卫生棉条 因为
I wanted to buy a degradable,
我想买一个可降解的
No problem. Just go right ahead.
没问题 请便
Just...
只是...
what's your problem?
你有什么问题？
Nothing.
什么都没有
Okay.
好的
People is so aggressive...
有些人总是如此咄咄逼人...
Reaper, it's Playboy. Abort. I need you to abort.
死神 是花花公子 取消 我需要你取消
Abort the last strike. I need you to abort the last...!
取消最后一次攻击 我需要你取消最后一次.....！
Fuck!
妈的
距离最后攻击的时间还剩
Call SitComm.
请致电总部
I don't understand.
我不明白
Call SitComm, for fuck's sake.
看在他妈的份上 打电话给总部
Calling SitComm.
呼叫总部
Come on!
来吧
Yeah!
是啊
Come on, motherfuckers. Answer the phone.
来吧 混蛋 接电话
Lining up for the final run.
准备好最后一次攻击
Come on. Call SitComm.
来吧 呼叫总部
Come on! Come on!
来吧！来吧！
Motherfucker,
狗娘养的
answer the fucking phone.
他妈的接电话
Come on!
快点
来吧
Oh, fuck it.
去他妈的
Fuck it!
Load 0-1 on final approach.
为最后一击装载 0-1
Come on.
来吧
Move! Move!
走 走
Right there.
就在那儿
Time to target
开火时间
30 seconds.
Guys!
伙计们
Come on, move!
快走
What the...
什么...
Impact 15 seconds.
Abort the strike!
取消攻击！
We have payload. Ten seconds.
载荷有效 10秒钟
Seven... six... five...
七 六 五
three, two, one...
三 二 一...
Boeing 0-1, abort! Boeing 0-1, abort!
波音0-1 终止 波音0-1 终止
Do you copy?
你收到了吗？
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
They copy?
他们收到没？
Yeah.
收到了
The operator
行动人员
is still in the target area.
仍在目标区域内
Bullshit.
胡说八道
Zoom in.
放大
Zoom in to the caves
放大到山洞那边
where the strike was gonna be
本来的攻击地点
There he is. That's him. That's Playboy.
就是他 就是他 这就是花花公子
Sorry, man.
对不起 伙计
Goddamn, Reaper.
该死的死神
Who...
谁...
are you waving at?
你在跟谁招手？
A friend.
一个朋友
Fuck!
妈的
Who won the game?
谁赢得了比赛？
Vols, baby.
狼队 宝贝
Elite eight.
八强
That's wonderful, Colonel,
太好了 上校
congratulations.
祝贺你
It's an excellent win for you
这对你和伟大的田纳西州来说
and the great state of Tennessee.
是一次绝佳的胜利
That's right.
说的没错
I just called that phone
我刚打了那个电话
five fucking times.
他妈的五次
Ringer's off again.
铃声又关了
Now it wasn't my pregnant wife.
现在不是我怀孕的妻子
But it was a life-or-death situation for a JTAC operator in the field.
但是 对于在战地现场的空管员来说 是一个生死攸关的时刻
Our job is communication!
我们的工作就是沟通！
Our priority is protecting the men and women
我们的首要任务是保护
who serve this country.
为国家服务的那些人
So if you don't mind,
如果你们不介意的话
can we get back on with the fucking job?
我们能继续他妈的工作吗？
Hell you think you're doing?
你以为你在干什么？
You can take that out of my active-duty bonuses, Colonel.
你可以从我的现役奖金中扣除 上校
Hey, get some sleep.
嘿 睡会儿吧
See you in the morning.
明早见
See you then.
到时候见
Uh...
呃...
you don't own a tux, do you?
你没有礼服吧？
A tux?
礼服？
I do not own a tux, no.
我没有礼服 没有
Okay.
好的
Wedding is not black tie, right?
婚礼不能系黑领带 对吗？
No, not black tie.
不 不能系黑领带
The wedding party is.
婚礼聚会上可以
Are you gonna ask me to be a bridesmaid?
你要邀请我做伴郎吗？
No, Reaper.
不 死神
I was gonna ask if you want to walk me down the aisle.
我想问你是否愿意陪我走红毯
You serious?
你是认真的吗？
Yeah.
是啊
Wow.
哇
That would be one of the greatest privileges of my life.
这将是我一生中最大的荣幸之一
You know one thing I know...
你知道我百分之百肯定的...
one hundred percent for sure.
一件事就是
Your dad
你爸爸
would be so proud of you.
会为你感到骄傲的
Thank you.
谢谢
So, what are we going to dance to?
那么 我们跳什么舞呢？
Dance?
跳舞？
Yeah.
是啊
Oh, no, I have not thought about that yet.
哦 不 我还没想过这个问题
Okay. Well, you got to pick a song
好吧 好吧 你得选一首歌
and then just listen to my hands.
然后就听我的手指挥
I'm gonna listen to your hands?
我要听你的手指挥？
- Oh, yeah. Yes, you are. - Oh, okay.
- 哦 是的 就是 - 哦 好吧
Whoa, okay.
哇 好吧
- Run this round my back. - This?
- 用这个绕过我的背 - 这个？
That way, I know where it's coming.
这样 我就知道它从哪里来了
- That's right. There you go. - Okay, what's next?
- 这就对了 这就对了 - 好吧 接下来呢？
- Come back in and out. - Out.
- 过来再出去 - 出来了
- And back to me. - Okay.
- 再回到我这边 - 好的
- And then out. - Out.
- 然后出去 - 出来了
This time around.
这一次转圈
Give me the other hand.
把另一只手给我
Oh okay.
哦 好吧
Walking over. Great
走过去 好极了
- Around my back. - Oh, around.
- 绕着我的背 - 哦 绕圈
Beautiful.
漂亮
You have done this many, many times before.
你以前已经做过很多次了
I've had a few Dosey Does.
我有过几次难忘的经历
Oh, you're pretty good. You're pretty good.
你真厉害 你真厉害
Any other dances. You know how to twerk?
还会其他舞蹈吗 你会扭屁股吗？
To who? To twerk?
扭什么？扭屁股?
To twerk.
扭屁股?
- Uh, no. I don't know how to twerk. - You better get practicing. Yeah.
- 呃 不 我不会扭屁股 - 你最好去练练 真的
《惊  天  激  战》
字幕:Dex7er  公众号:值得看的